(Sheldon:)...and since Howard and Bernadette are
married, intellectual property in the letter...
(Sheldon:)...is jointly owned by the two spouses?
(Penny:)Yeah, obviously.
(Sheldon:)Well played.
(Sheldon:)Sometimes I don't give you
enough credit, Penny.
(Raj:)Dude, you made the right choice
coming to me for help with this party.
(Leonard:)Actually, all I did was invite you.
(Raj:)Well, put your mind at ease.
(Raj:)I'm here to make sure your dinner party
kicks Howard's dinner party's ass.
(Raj:)Now, the first thing we need is a theme.
(Raj:)I'm thinking, ah,
turn-of-the-century Moulin Rouge.
(Leonard:)I'm thinking you need a testosterone patch.
Penny and I just wanna
do something low-key.
(Leonard:)You know, cocktails, light jazz music,
hors d'oeuvres.
So your theme is "I saw a rerun of Mad Men
and bought crab puffs from Trader Joe's"?